https://www.vitrolife.com/customer-service/privacy-policy/

Privacy policy
Vitrolife Sweden AB (“Vitrolife” or “we”) cares about your privacy. Therefore, Vitrolife always strives to protect your personal data in the best possible way and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations for the protection of personal data.
This privacy policy includes information about how Vitrolife process personal data about you as a:
representative of a customer, potential customer or former customer;
representative of a supplier or partner;
subscriber of Vitrolife’s marketing, news and information;
user of Vitrolife’s e-learning tools, web and/or webshop (including social media);
participant in an event (including Capital Markets Day) arranged or coordinated by Vitrolife; and
shareholder or a representative of a shareholder of Vitrolife.
In summary, we conduct all our processing of your personal data for the following overall purposes:
communicate with you as representative of a customer, potential customer, former customer, supplier or partner, including having contact with you to negotiate and close an agreement with the company you represent;
administrate any agreements with the company you represent;
communicate offers, news, updates, market studies or product evaluations to you – this may include profiling as described below;
upon request by you as representative of a customer: register and thereafter administrate a webshop user account;
store any responses you’ve made to our social media posts;
administrate our events (including Capital Markets Day);
contact you as a shareholder or a representative of a shareholder and administrate and fulfill the rights of the shareholder, including administrating the general meeting of shareholders; and
comply with any applicable laws and regulations which require processing of your personal data, for example any traceability requirements or accounting and bookkeeping requirement.
Do you want to know more about how we process your personal data? Download the full Privacy Policy here.
All content © Vitrolife 2020. Products shown on this website might not be available on all markets.
Privacy policy
Disclaimer
